<Document>
  # Hearts

  Every living creature has a heart inside them, unless youre a heartless bastard of course.
  Hearts are simple, if they beat its fine, if they dont, well that sucks.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OrganHumanHeart" />
  </Box>

  Every heart has a BPM, meaning BeatsPerMinute, on a standard human its 100 beats per minute
  anything more or less that that is bad, meaning something is wrong with the heart.

  For a normal human, anything more than 150 or less than 50 means that the heart is in fibrillations.

  Fibrillations can be countered in many ways some are:

  - if the heart is lacking BPM, then some hard drugs or using a defibrillator might work.
  - if the heart is beating more than it needs to, some relaxing drugs or a defibrillator might work.

  hard drugs are, for example, ephedrine or desoxyephedrine, cocaine, etc.
  relaxing drugs are fentanyl and others.

  ## Defibrillator usage

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Defibrillator" />
  </Box>

  The defibrillators found shiftstart in medical are [bold]MANUAL DEFIBRILLATORS[/bold] and they require proper use.

  The ones that science can print and those found in paramedics lockers are called compact defibrillators (sometimes, an auto defibrillators or AEDs)

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="DefibrillatorCompact" Caption="compact defibrillator" />
  </Box>

  AEDs or compact defibrillators are easy in use, as they will try to change the BPM of the target by 45 closest to the standard BPM of the patient.

  Manual defibrillators need to be properly used to not cause death to the patient.

  # Manual Defibrillator Guide

  M.E.D.s have 4 switches and one power flip, with a screen that tells the current heartrate of the patient.
  By interacting with the defib onto yourself or any other living creature, it will switch the monitor to the patient, showing his BPM.

  The flips and switches do the following:

  - IO switch (power switch) - O is Off, I is ON.
  - Voltage flips - 4 identical switches, that raise the voltage of the defibrillator by 500V each.

  - 1 flip/500V - Lowers the BPM by 80, useful if the BPM of the patient is in 200+
  - 2 flips/1000V - Lowers the BPM by 50, useful if the BPM of the patient is around 200
  - 3 flips/1500V - Raises the BPM by 150-200, useful if the patient is flatlined (has 0 BPM)
  - 4 flips/2000V - Raises the BPM by 200-300, useful always never



</Document>
